NI Malcolm Johnson

UI/UX Designer

314 224 9696 malcolmdjohnson@gmail.com malcolmtosh.com

Expertise

I am a digital designer and marketer with over a decade of experience. I have helped create digital products across a variety of industries, some of which include: automotive, higher education, food, and health care. I believe in using design to make things beautiful and easy to use.

Experience

UI/UX Designer | H&L Partners

March 2020 — Present

Design UI/UX for websites and applications; develop HTML5 banners. Clients: McDonald's, Toyota and AAA.

Freelancer | malcolmtosh.com

January 2009 — Present

I help businesses and entrepreneurs actualize their digital advertising goals.

Graphic Artist | Ansira

April 2013 — March 2020

Created digital and traditional media advertising templates for co-ops. Clients: Acura, Honda, Ferrari, Alfa Romeo, VW, Lincoln, and Planet Fitness.

Digital Marketing Coordinator | Wash U. School of Medicine in St. Louis August 2014 — January 2015

Co-led the website redesign project for the Siteman Cancer Center. Created content for the social media platforms and measured their effectiveness.

Education

M.A. in Advertising & Marketing Communications | Webster University July 2013

B.S. in Marketing | Missouri State University July 2009